接下来我们来看看如何实现它。
All right, you're done. Let's talk about how I
首先，把我们的代码
solved this one. First, let's take all our code, and
从FetchWeatherTask中拷贝出来
copy it from the fetch weather task. The intent
IntentService中会创建一个helper线程来运行这部分代码
service actually creates a helper thread for us to run
和AsyncTask所做的工作类似。
on. Similar to what async task does. So we
我们仅需要把这部分代码从doBackground拷贝到
can just copy this stuff from doing background to on
handleIntent中即可。这里我们添加一些辅助的常量。比如LOG_TAG
handle intent. Let's add a few helpful constants, such as
和Intent Extra所需的String常量，
log tag and an Intent Extra, so we can pass
这样我们就能传递位置请求了。
in the location query. Now, we're just going to
现在我们仅需要整体浏览一遍代码，清除一下里面的错误即可。
go through and clean up some of the errors.
Intent Service没有返回值。
After all, Intent Service doesn't return a value. And
而且由于它是一个服务，因此它有自己的Context(上下文)
since it's a service, it has its own context.
就是这样，我们已经把我们的FetchWeatherTask变成了
And that's it. We've turned our fetch weather task
IntentService，非常“简单粗暴”。
into an intents service, pretty straightforward. Now we just
下面我们需要调用它。在ForecastFragment的
need to call it. So, now in the update
updateWeather函数中，我可以通过显式Intent的方式
weather function from within forecast fragment, we can call
调用服务
the service using an explicit intent,
将所需的参数放到Intent Extra中
putting the parameter into an intent extra.
那么接下来我们看看它的运行效果
All right, let's take a look at how that runs. And when we
当我们点击“refresh”按钮时，它会调用我们的新服务。非常棒！
hit the refresh button, it'll use our new service. Pretty nice. And we
这货和我们所构思的一模一样。
really can't tell any difference, which is how we'd expect things to be.